I command that infirmity to leave you, in the name of Jesus!
I command that demon – all his sickness, setback and hardship to leave you, in the name of Jesus!
Leave my people!
You demon - leave my people!
Prayer!
Cockroach Vomited During Mass Prayer
Watch your screen.
See what faith can do.
Cockroach Vomited During Mass Prayer
I have seen Jesus walking in the Spirit.
I have seen power of Jesus walking in the Spirit.
I have seen the Word of God walking in the Spirit.
Cockroach Vomited During Mass Prayer
See what has happened - that is the power of God.
Hallelujah!
This is the lady who during the time of the mass prayer with Prophet T.B. Joshua vomited this large insect,
which has a form of a cockroach.
You can see it in the midst of some vomit, which has very vile smell.
Right now, we want to hear from the lady herself.
Madam, you're welcome.
Can you tell us your name and where are you from?
My name is Chantel Bridget.
I come from Cameroon.
What was the problem you were having?
The problem I had was blockage and I ate in the dream all the time.
I had a moving object in my womb, all the time, which caused miscarriages.
Recently, my children started dying and something was moving in my womb.
You mean that any time you would be pregnant something would stop the pregnancy,
something would eat the child in your womb?
Yes.
What happened to you during the time of the mass prayer?
What did you feel?
During the mass prayer, I started feeling strong pain all over my womb.
Something was turning round and around in my womb.
After that I started vomiting and I vomited this insect.
I thank God; now, I am free!
How do you feel while pressing your stomach now?
Are you feeling any pain?
Nothing! Now, I am free.
Thank You, Jesus for delivering me and my family.
Amen. We give all glory to God.
We thank Him for delivering her.
She is free from this moving object, which she vomited during the mass prayer -
it came out in the form of a cockroach.
That is what you are seeing right now on the floor.
This happened some moments ago, letting us know that there is never a problem you cannot solve,
never a burden Jesus Christ cannot bear.
This happened just now, during the mass prayer time when Prophet T.B. Joshua was praying
along with people here and with those watching - and this is what happened.
This lady was delivered, set free from this problem of moving object, which came out in a form of a cockroach,
when she vomited it during this time.
We give all glory to God.
She is rejoicing now.
She says the pain she was feeling before has gone from the womb.
Today she is delivered and set free.
Thank You, Jesus!
Thank You, Jesus for delivering me and my family.
TESTIMONY TIME
Good morning church!
[Good morning.]
My names are Chantal Bridget Nyemeck.
I come from Cameroon.
The problem that brought me here was evil attack and moving object in my womb.
This evil attack manifested in that I usually saw dead people,
even my husband who is dead, in my dream.
I ate in the dream and drank in the dream.
I usually saw myself in dirty places, old houses and things that were very dirty.
And I have spirit...
On the other side, I had a spiritual husband and small children.
On this side, I had big children.
All the time, I had moving objects in my body.
I usually watched Emmanuel TV in Cameroon.
I had a dream and saw the man of God.
He asked me, "My daughter, why does everybody hate you?"
He carried me like a baby and threw me in the water.
People around me started clapping, "You are saved!"
That was why I came here, to look for a solution to my case.
OK. So, we are listening to what our sister is saying; how she actually had a dream before coming to The SCOAN
after praying along with Prophet T.B Joshua on Emmanuel TV.
In that world, where she used to see herself in the dream, which is full of dead people
she actually saw Prophet T.B. Joshua and he placed her in water and her body was cleansed.
Is that right, madam?
Yes, he threw me in a big river and I washed myself.
After that, people around me were clapping, "You have changed, madam".
Last week you came to The SCOAN.
Tell us what happened during the mass prayer.
During the mass prayer, I was sitting over there.
I prayed, "God, can I return to Cameroon with the same case? God, do my own today, please".
During the mass prayer when the man of God prayed, he did not touch me.
I prayed; after some time, I felt pain in my womb.
I turned and begun to vomit poison; then, I vomited this cockroach.
Hallelujah! Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
Our sister is explaining that as the mass prayer was going on she felt the power of God move around her
and her stomach.
At that minute madam, what happened to you, as you began to feel the sensation in your stomach?
What happened next?
After I vomited, the pain stopped.
Now, I sleep well.
I don’t see dead people in my dream any more.
I sleep well, like a baby.
That is why I came here to testify.
Amen. Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
So, when you vomited out that cockroach, that insect' immediately after that
you realized that the moving object in your body disappeared.
The moving object has stopped.
Now, I'm feeling fine; I am fine.
And you began to sleep well, no more nightmares - is that right?
Yes.
Amen. Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
So, can you just touch your stomach now?
How are you feeling after the prayer?
No, I am fine; nothing hurts in my body.
Well, thank You, Jesus Christ.
Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ.
We can just imagine - what we have seen on the screen here; that cockroach was the physical manifestation
of that spirit that had actually been destroying our sister's life.
You listened to her; how she had been plagued with terrible nightmares, seeing herself in the midst
of dead people, with a strange man - her husband in the dream, in another world.
As Prophet T.B. Joshua prayed, the power of God flowed through her body.
We see how she vomited out this insect and ever since then she has been completely free,
and she has been sleeping like a baby, to the glory of God.
So, one more time, let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ.
Madam, what can you say about this insect that came out?
Were you surprised to see such a thing coming out?
I don't want to see it again.
I am afraid of it when I see it.
Our sister was shocked to see such an object coming out of her.
But, to the glory of God, she is free now.
Finally madam, what is your word of advice to our viewers all over the world?
My advice goes like this: trust God; have faith.
It may be one year, two years or ten years but God will remember you.
One day, you will receive your own testimony like me.
Amen. Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ.
Emmanuel!
(God With Us – Matthew 1:23)
My name is Chantal Bridget Neymeck.
I come from Cameroon.
The problem that brought me to The SCOAN
were evil attack in my dreams and moving objects in my womb.
These problems affected my life; I couldn't laugh and cried everywhere I went.
That was why I decided to come to The SCOAN, looking for a solution to my problems.
Tell us, when you came to The SCOAN, what happened to you.
On that day during the mass prayer, I asked God, "Can I return to Cameroon with the same case?
God, please help me".
I didn’t finish my prayer when I felt a very bad pain in my womb.
As the man of God started praying, during the mass prayer, my senses were gone and I started vomiting.
On that day, everyone saw me vomit a cockroach.
After I vomited it, the pain stopped.
I didn’t feel anything; my womb is OK.
Everything is OK.
That is why I thank God.
Now, I sleep well – like a baby.
I have no bad dreams anymore, no pain anymore and I eat.
Since that day, I have not seen any evil thing again in my dreams.
As I told you before - I sleep well.
We really thank God for what God has done in your life.
We want you to know that man of God loves you and your family so much.
After that prayer of the man of God, and now, when we know that God Almighty has solved your problem
and healed you completely of your sickness; tell us about your condition as a widow.
It is a very bad experience; since I lost my husband, there has been nothing to eat.
My children couldn't go to school.
I needed to do anything to eat.
But starting today, that situation has ended.
Tell us what kind of things were you doing just to feed you and your children.
I usually sold peanuts in the market in my country and cleaned houses for wealthy people
before I would be able to eat.
So, more or less, you were like a housemaid?
Yes.
Now, how do you feel, knowing that the God Almighty has healed you
and is also about to bless you abundantly?
Now, I'm very happy; I don’t know how to explain my happiness.
I'm very happy; man of God, be blessed!
The man of God in his grace and mercy is giving you this gift of morning water with the booklet
and also he is blessing you with the mirror - a book that will show you what you were, what you are,
and what you are about to be in the future.
Finally, he is blessing you with the sum of 200 000 naira to help your financial needs
and to take care of your family and your children.
Wow, I didn’t expect to receive this huge amount of money; I'm very happy!
Now, I am healed; I am blessed.
It is enough money for me; when I return to Cameroon, I will start a business,
train my children and pay their school fees.
Everything will be fine.
Amen. Indeed, we thank God for what the Lord has done in your life
and we are also happy and we rejoice with you.
We want to encourage you to continue to make God's Word the standard for your life.
Remember, you have been delivered by the Word of God - you need to go and continue to be ruled by His Word,
in Jesus' name.
Amen!
Man of God, thank you; you will be blessed!
The advice I need to give people all over the world who are looking at me is:
you need to have faith.
No matter what you are passing through, you need to have faith.
You need to come to this place.
It is a final place you were looking for.
I thank God.